adgully.com 2017-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Adgully

PRIVACY POLICY

Data on this site belongs to Adgully and has been checked independently. We however, request you to check with relevant agencies before taking any business decisions based on our data. All press releases are either provided directly by the client or by their PR agency

www.adgully.com (hereinafter referred to as "ADGULLY Site") is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. The following guidelines discloses the privacy practices for www.adgully.com

**A. Process of Collecting Information**

The information gathered by ADGULLY Site falls into three categories:

Information voluntarily supplied by subscribers to our websites through optional registration for receiving information and updates

Information voluntarily supplied by subscribers to our websites through optional registration for enlisting as Freelancers for providing freelancing services and Clients for obtaining freelancing services.

Tracking information gathered as subscribers navigate through our sites.

**B. Utilizing the Collected Information and Placing Cookies**

To make use of certain features on our websites, subscribers must provide certain information as part of the registration process. (We may ask, for example, for your name, email address, sex, and age, and we might request information on your profession/ occupation, interests, and the like.) The information you supply will help us to make ADGULLY Site a better website by allowing us to tailor our site to your interests and make it more useful to you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. Moreover, the information supplied by you is subject to verification as in many cases where the subscriber has enlisted as a Freelancer, the content delivered by him to the client has to be within the legal framework of the internet subject to the Indian Laws. In some instances, which involve, for example, subscriptions, you may need to provide all the information before the subscription can reach you if we don't know how to contact you. Of course, even if you want to remain completely anonymous, you are still free to take advantage of the wealth of content available on our site without providing any personal information.

To help make our websites more responsive to the needs of our subscribers, we invoke a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie". We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable the Site to relate your use of the Site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to the ADGULLY Site. We use cookies to help us tailor our sites to meet your needs, and to deliver a better service that is keyed to the interests of our subscribers. We use cookies to determine what features our subscribers prefer and which are less popular. We can build a better site if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple process to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information on this process.

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our websites. Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our websites to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our websites and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our subscribers come.

**C. Privacy policy exclusively applies to www.adgully.com**

www.adgully.com includes links to other websites whose privacy policies we do not control. Once you leave our servers use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.

**D. Statistics and Storage**

When we present information to our advertisers to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites. It is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our sites. If you do register with ADGULLY Site, we may, from time to time, contact you about content and features that we believe may be of interest to you.

All information gathered on www.adgully.com is securely stored within the ADGULLY Site controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

**Amendment to the Privacy Guidelines**

If we need to change our privacy guidelines at some point in the future, we'll post the changes before they take effect. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

If at any time you believe this ADGULLY Site has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail to feedback@adgully.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem. If you have questions about this policy, please e-mail us at feedback@adgully.com

**Copyright and Intellectual Property Policy**

Adgully! respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users to do the same. Adgully! has no responsibility for content on other web sites that you may find or access when using Adgully! products or services. Material available on or through other web sites may be protected by copyright and the intellectual property laws of India and/or other countries. The terms of use of those web sites, and not the Adgully! Terms of Service, govern your use of that material.

It is Adgully’s! policy, in appropriate circumstances and at its discretion, to disable and/or terminate the accounts of users who may infringe or repeatedly infringe the copyrights or other intellectual property rights of Adgully! and/ or others.

Information to Copyright Officer for Infringement of Intellectual Property Violations.

If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, or that your intellectual property rights have been otherwise violated, please provide Adgully! Copyright Officer with the following information:

name, address, telephone number, and email address of the original owner of the copyright or other intellectual property interest;

a description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed;

a description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Adgully! site, with enough detail that we may find it on the web site;

your name address, telephone number, and email address;

a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright or intellectual property owner, its agent, or the law;

Adgully! Copyright Officer for infringement of copyright or other intellectual property infringement can be reached as follows:

By Mail

Copyright Officer c/o Adgully!  
Adgully Network Pvt Ltd  
'C' Wing, 310, Twin Arcade,  
Military Road, Marol,  
Andheri (E)  
Mumbai - 400 059   
India   
By email: webmaster@adgully.com

**Permissions**

If you are seeking permission to use Adgully! trademarks, logos, service marks, slogans, screen shots, copyrighted designs, or other brand features, please contact the copyright officer.

Copyright © 2016 - Adgully.com   | Contactus   | About Us   | Terms & Conditions
